Ihsan Nurul Habib

+6287822697534 - ihsan.inh@gmail.com Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ihsaninh/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Oct 2023 - present

Frontend Developer

PT XL Axiata Tbk.

- Slicing UI design to App using Next.js and Tailwind CSS.
- Seamlessly integrated APIs to fetch and display data from the backend.
- Diagnose and fix bugs and performance bottlenecks for performance that feels smooth.
- Create a new feature for biometric registration using AWS Amplify Face Recognition to verify real users when registering a new XL or Axis number.

Sep 2019 - Aug 2023

Frontend Developer

Axiata Digital Labs

As Frontend Developer

- AKBAR (Web) Jun 2023 to Aug 2023
- eMR (Web) Aug 2022 to Aug 2023
- NewXlife (Web) Aug 2021 to Aug 2023

Task Completed:

- 1. Slicing UI design to App using Angular CLI and Tailwind CSS.
- 2. Seamlessly integrated APIs to fetch and display data from the backend.
- 3. Diagnose and fix bugs and performance bottlenecks for performance that feels native.
- Participated in all scrum ceremonies such as backlog grooming, sprint retrospective and Daily
- 5. Stand up.
- 6. Take part in the deployment process.

As Mobile Developer

- Boost Preneur (Mobile) Nov 2019 to Aug 2019
- Boost Penjual (Mobile) Sep 2019 to Nov 2019

Task Completed:

- 1. This is a mobile-based application developed with React Native technology.
- 2. Performing api integration from the backend.
- 3. Develop new features and bug fixing.
- 4. Slicing UI design to App using React Native components.

www.kalibrr.com Page 1 of 3

- 5. Seamlessly integrated APIs to fetch and display data from the backend.
- 6. Participated in all scrum ceremonies such as backlog grooming, sprint retrospective and Daily Stand up.
- 7. Take part in the deployment process.

Aug 2019 - present

Full Stack Developer

PT METEOR INOVASI DIGITAL

- Implemented responsive design principles to ensure seamless user experiences across different devices both web and mobile.
- Working with different technologies such as React Native for Mobile project and Next Js for Web projects.
- Seamlessly integrated APIs to fetch and display data from the backend.
- Developed new features and improved existing functionalities to enhance the user experience and meet project requirements.
- Participated in all scrum ceremonies such as backlog grooming, sprint planning, sprint retrospective and Daily Stand up.
- Take part in the deployment process.

EDUCATION

Jun 2019 - Jul 2019

Industrial Technology

Arkademy Pijar Camp

Embark on an intensive 1.5-month Bootcamp Trainee Program designed to immerse you in the world of application and website development using React Native and Express.js. This meticulously structured program aims to equip you with the essential skills and hands-on experience needed to excel in the tech industry.

Jun 2016 - Jun 2019

SMKN 2 BOGOR

Computer & Network Engineering

PERSONAL STATEMENT

I am a front-end developer with over 4 years of experience in the tech industry. Currently, I am using NextJS in my project and also have a understanding of other technologies such as React, React Native, and Angular. In addition, I am also currently learning other technologies such as Android Kotlin and Flutter.

I have the ability to work as part of a team or independently as needed for project requirements and am continuously learning new technologies to continually improve my skills.

I believe that with the skills I possess, I can make valuable contributions to the company I work for and continue to develop myself in this field.

SKILLS

- Next.Is
- React Native
- React JS

www.kalibrr.com Page 2 of 3

- Angular
- Typescript
- Android Development

CERTIFICATIONS AND LICENSES

Aug 2019

Mar 2024

Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Belajar Dasar AWS Cloud)
Dicoding Indonesia

Dec 2022

Belajar Fundamental Aplikasi Android
Dicoding Indonesia

Apr 2022

Pemrograman Kotlin: Pemula sampai Mahir
Udemy

Apr 2022

Belajar Prinsip Pemrograman SOLID
Dicoding Academy

Certificate of Graduation - Full Stack Software Developer

Pijar Camp

www.kalibrr.com
 Page 3 of 3